# -*- coding: utf-8 -*-

questions = [ # beginning of a list
{
  'question':'Which of these kills its victims by constriction?',
  'answers': {
    'a': 'Andalucia',
    'b': 'Anaconda',
    'c': 'Andypandy',
    'd': 'Annerobinson'
  },
  'correct':'b'
},
{
  'question':'Which of these might be used in underwater naval operations?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Frogmen',
    'b':'Newtmen',
    'c':'Toadmen',
    'd':'Tadpolemen'
    },
  'correct':'a'
},
{
  'question':'What are you said to do to a habit when you break it?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Throw it',
    'b':'Punch it',
    'c':'Kick it',
    'd':'Eat it'
    },
  'correct':'c'
},
{
  'question':'Where do you proverbially wear your heart, if you show your true feelings?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'On your collar',
    'b':'On your lapel',
    'c':'On your cuff',
    'd':'On your sleeve'
    },
  'correct':'d'
},
{
  'question':'What might an electrician lay?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Tables',
    'b':'Gables',
    'c':'Cables',
    'd':'Stables'
    },
  'correct':'c'
},
{
  'question':'Which colour is used as a term to describe an illegal market in rare goods?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Blue',
    'b':'Red',
    'c':'Black',
    'd':'White'
    },
  'correct':'c'
},
{
  'question':'What name is given to the person who traditionally attends the groom on his wedding day?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Best man',
    'b':'Top man',
    'c':'Old man',
    'd':'Poor man'
    },
  'correct':'a'
},
{
  'question':'Which country is not an island?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Madagascar',
    'b':'Cuba',
    'c':'Jamaica',
    'd':'Germany'
    },
  'correct':'d'
},
{
  'question':'Which is not the name of an English county?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Lancashire',
    'b':'Leicestershire',
    'c':'Liverpoolshire',
    'd':'Lincolnshire'
    },
  'correct':'c'
},
{
  'question':'What would you normally do with a beret?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Eat it',
    'b':'Play it',
    'c':'Sit on it',
    'd':'Wear it'
    },
  'correct':'d'
},
{
  'question':'According to the old adage, how many lives does a cat have?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Five',
    'b':'Seven',
    'c':'Nine',
    'd':'Ten'
    },
  'correct':'c'
},
{
  'question':'Which part of the human body encases many of the vital organs such as the heart, lungs and liver?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Head',
    'b':'Torso',
    'c':'Legs',
    'd':'Arms'
    },
  'correct':'b'
},
{
  'question':'In which of the following might food be stored?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Larder',
    'b':'Shed',
    'c':'Greenhouse',
    'd':'Garage'
    },
  'correct':'a'
},
{
  'question':'What type of protective headgear do motorcyclists wear?',
  'answers': {
    'a':'Bash helmet',
    'b':'Crash helmet',
    'c':'Mash helmet',
    'd':'Flash helmet'
    },
  'correct':'b'
}
] # end of a list
